*HASH_VALUE	outpost ID	name	description
_65A3A9829307D1F6	fyros_outpost_04.outpost	Malmont Farm	Outpost founded in 2489, abandoned in 2494\n Challenge for expert-rank guilds\n An outpost constructed to the south of the Malmount and the Dragon's Tail, its activity concentrated on mining resources in this hostile region. A portion of its resources were transported to the village of Dyron and the two workshops nearby. The remaining materials were brought along the road to Pyr under heavy escort.
_521819DBD72AB7EE	marauder_light_melee_fighter_b.outpost_squad	Marauder Warriors Squad	
_521819DBD72ABBEE	marauder_light_melee_fighter_c.outpost_squad	Marauder Warriors Squad	
_521819DBD72ABFEE	marauder_light_melee_fighter_d.outpost_squad	Marauder Warriors Squad	
_521819DBD72AC3EE	marauder_light_melee_fighter_e.outpost_squad	Marauder Warriors Squad	
_521819DBD72AC7EE	marauder_light_melee_fighter_f.outpost_squad	Marauder Warriors Squad	
_4F35552030D28537	marauder_light_range_fighter_b.outpost_squad	Marauder Range Fighters Squad	
_4F35552030D28937	marauder_light_range_fighter_c.outpost_squad	Marauder Range Fighters Squad	
_4F35552030D28D37	marauder_light_range_fighter_d.outpost_squad	Marauder Range Fighters Squad	
_4F35552030D29137	marauder_light_range_fighter_e.outpost_squad	Marauder Range Fighters Squad	
_4F35552030D29537	marauder_light_range_fighter_f.outpost_squad	Marauder Range Fighters Squad	
_127875D514AA73EE	marauder_light_mixed_fighter_b.outpost_squad	Marauder Fighters Squad	
_127875D514AA77EE	marauder_light_mixed_fighter_c.outpost_squad	Marauder Fighters Squad	
_127875D514AA7BEE	marauder_light_mixed_fighter_d.outpost_squad	Marauder Fighters Squad	
_127875D514AA7FEE	marauder_light_mixed_fighter_e.outpost_squad	Marauder Fighters Squad	
_127875D514AA83EE	marauder_light_mixed_fighter_f.outpost_squad	Marauder Fighters Squad	
_AA27968E684160C8	free_squad_light_melee_fighter_b.outpost_squad	Militiamen Squad	A squad of eight apprentice mercenaries, composed of warriors and two healers, equipped with rapid weapons and light armour.
_BF143CBC2BFD49D9	free_squad_light_melee_fighter_c.outpost_squad	Militiamen Squad	A squad of eight confirmed mercenaries, composed of warriors and two healers, equipped with rapid weapons and light armour.
_43CBC8DDF75D280B	free_squad_light_melee_fighter_d.outpost_squad	Militiamen Squad	A squad of eight advanced mercenaries, composed of warriors and two healers, equipped with rapid weapons and light armour.
_84ED251CBB1400E3	free_squad_light_melee_fighter_e.outpost_squad	Militiamen Squad	A squad of eight expert mercenaries, composed of warriors and two healers, equipped with rapid weapons and light armour.
_41DE3105FD1400E1	free_squad_light_melee_fighter_f.outpost_squad	Militiamen Squad	A squad of eight master mercenaries, composed of warriors and two healers, equipped with rapid weapons and light armour.
_FF0CB4F681F74244	outpost_squad_light_melee_fighter_b.outpost_squad	Squad of skirmishers	A squad of eight apprentice mercenaries, composed of warriors and two healers, equipped with rapid weapons and light armour
_4363F04E8097317E	outpost_squad_light_melee_fighter_c.outpost_squad	Squad of skirmishers	A squad of eight confirmed mercenaries, composed of warriors and two healers, equipped with rapid weapons and light armour
_CF901D3115994936	outpost_squad_light_melee_fighter_d.outpost_squad	Squad of skirmishers	A squad of eight advanced mercenaries, composed of warriors and two healers, equipped with rapid weapons and light armour
_C6F26688E51CB73E	outpost_squad_light_melee_fighter_e.outpost_squad	Squad of skirmishers	A squad of eight expert mercenaries, composed of warriors and two healers, equipped with rapid weapons and light armour
_4531A28B1F9CB73E	outpost_squad_light_melee_fighter_f.outpost_squad	Squad of skirmishers	A squad of eight master mercenaries, composed of warriors and two healers, equipped with rapid weapons and light armour
_C5BF158CD8504200	outpost_squad_medium_melee_fighter_b.outpost_squad	Squad of battlers	A squad of eight apprentice mercenaries, composed of warriors in medium armor equipped with light weapons, some carrying a shield, and a healer
_086B6B9A3CA17751	outpost_squad_medium_melee_fighter_c.outpost_squad	Squad of battlers	A squad of eight confirmed mercenaries, composed of warriors in medium armor equipped with light weapons, some carrying a shield, and a healer
_9BE9B6F17BBDA89E	outpost_squad_medium_melee_fighter_d.outpost_squad	Squad of battlers	A squad of eight advanced mercenaries, composed of warriors in medium armor equipped with light weapons, some carrying a shield, and a healer
_85B573A73C138793	outpost_squad_medium_melee_fighter_e.outpost_squad	Squad of battlers	A squad of eight expert mercenaries, composed of warriors in medium armor equipped with light weapons, some carrying a shield, and a healer
_C5B56B9A00432B9B	outpost_squad_medium_melee_fighter_f.outpost_squad	Squad of battlers	A squad of eight master mercenaries, composed of warriors in medium armor equipped with light weapons, some carrying a shield, and a healer
_14147A69FC5CC445	outpost_squad_heavy_melee_fighter_b.outpost_squad	Squad of heavy warriors	A squad of eight apprentice mercenaries, composed of warriors in heavy armor equipped with two-handed weapons, and a healer
_F6C3A9AD2C915DE9	outpost_squad_heavy_melee_fighter_c.outpost_squad	Squad of heavy warriors	A squad of eight confirmed mercenaries, composed of warriors in heavy armor equipped with two-handed weapons, and a healer
_E4BC11753CDDAF46	outpost_squad_heavy_melee_fighter_d.outpost_squad	Squad of heavy warriors	A squad of eight advanced mercenaries, composed of warriors in heavy armor equipped with two-handed weapons, and a healer
_CF2E06DB24FDEF5D	outpost_squad_heavy_melee_fighter_e.outpost_squad	Squad of heavy warriors	A squad of eight expert mercenaries, composed of warriors in heavy armor equipped with two-handed weapons, and a healer
_8FCD26DB24DDBB6C	outpost_squad_heavy_melee_fighter_f.outpost_squad	Squad of heavy warriors	A squad of eight master mercenaries, composed of warriors in heavy armor equipped with two-handed weapons, and a healer
_D1DECB0C0956E6FF	outpost_squad_tank_b.outpost_squad	Squad of protectors	A squad of eight apprentice mercenaries, composed of warriors in heavy armor equipped with light weapons and shields, and a healer
_D7088C97BA526CF3	outpost_squad_tank_c.outpost_squad	Squad of protectors	A squad of eight confirmed mercenaries, composed of warriors in heavy armor equipped with light weapons and shields, and a healer
_D587B2DB1D819C90	outpost_squad_tank_d.outpost_squad	Squad of protectors	A squad of eight advanced mercenaries, composed of warriors in heavy armor equipped with light weapons and shields, and a healer
_F4C3F776D24CE121	outpost_squad_tank_e.outpost_squad	Squad of protectors	A squad of eight expert mercenaries, composed of warriors in heavy armor equipped with light weapons and shields, and a healer
_B3F233790CCCE121	outpost_squad_tank_f.outpost_squad	Squad of protectors	A squad of eight master mercenaries, composed of warriors in heavy armor equipped with light weapons and shields, and a healer
_41B924D5193F03EE	outpost_squad_light_range_fighter_b.outpost_squad	Squad of gunfighters	A squad of eight apprentice mercenaries, composed of shooters in medium armor equipped with pistols, and a healer
_AE8F7C13BB9ECC89	outpost_squad_light_range_fighter_c.outpost_squad	Squad of gunfighters	A squad of eight confirmed mercenaries, composed of shooters in medium armor equipped with pistols, and a healer
_53CA49FD090794B7	outpost_squad_light_range_fighter_d.outpost_squad	Squad of gunfighters	A squad of eight advanced mercenaries, composed of shooters in medium armor equipped with pistols, and a healer
_E299971DA36AB732	outpost_squad_light_range_fighter_e.outpost_squad	Squad of gunfighters	A squad of eight expert mercenaries, composed of shooters in medium armor equipped with pistols, and a healer
_61D8D320DDEAB732	outpost_squad_light_range_fighter_f.outpost_squad	Squad of gunfighters	A squad of eight master mercenaries, composed of shooters in medium armor equipped with pistols, and a healer
_0DF4D7484C79975C	outpost_squad_medium_range_fighter_b.outpost_squad	Squad of gunners	A squad of eight apprentice mercenaries, composed of shooters in medium armor equipped with rifles, and a healer
_9A2753D9DD62C9D3	outpost_squad_medium_range_fighter_c.outpost_squad	Squad of gunners	A squad of eight confirmed mercenaries, composed of shooters in medium armor equipped with rifles, and a healer
_79F80F704137D456	outpost_squad_medium_range_fighter_d.outpost_squad	Squad of gunners	A squad of eight advanced mercenaries, composed of shooters in medium armor equipped with rifles, and a healer
_0C6BA6E67A9BF767	outpost_squad_medium_range_fighter_e.outpost_squad	Squad of gunners	A squad of eight expert mercenaries, composed of shooters in medium armor equipped with rifles, and a healer
_4E6BA6E4378C0350	outpost_squad_medium_range_fighter_f.outpost_squad	Squad of gunners	A squad of eight master mercenaries, composed of shooters in medium armor equipped with rifles, and a healer
_83B9D6A14775D36C	outpost_squad_heavy_range_fighter_b.outpost_squad	Squad of artillery shooters	A squad of eight apprentice mercenaries, composed of shooters equipped with machine guns and grenade launchers, and a healer
_B88A2ADC3D37B4BA	outpost_squad_heavy_range_fighter_c.outpost_squad	Squad of artillery shooters	A squad of eight confirmed mercenaries, composed of shooters equipped with machine guns and grenade launchers, and a healer
_4A265EE81064A4EE	outpost_squad_heavy_range_fighter_d.outpost_squad	Squad of artillery shooters	A squad of eight advanced mercenaries, composed of shooters equipped with machine guns and grenade launchers, and a healer
_D8BF17CCD52A49CB	outpost_squad_heavy_range_fighter_e.outpost_squad	Squad of artillery shooters	A squad of eight expert mercenaries, composed of shooters equipped with machine guns and grenade launchers, and a healer
_D8AFE3DB95B969CB	outpost_squad_heavy_range_fighter_f.outpost_squad	Squad of artillery shooters	A squad of eight master mercenaries, composed of shooters equipped with machine guns and grenade launchers, and a healer
_904A71ECA09309EE	outpost_squad_light_mixed_fighter_b.outpost_squad	Squad of harriers	A squad of eight apprentice mercenaries, composed of warriors and shooters equipped with rapid weapons and pistols, and a healer
_D5C630F24DC26BF6	outpost_squad_light_mixed_fighter_c.outpost_squad	Squad of harriers	A squad of eight confirmed mercenaries, composed of warriors and shooters equipped with rapid weapons and pistols, and a healer
_D8A5FB5A0DE0C785	outpost_squad_light_mixed_fighter_d.outpost_squad	Squad of harriers	A squad of eight advanced mercenaries, composed of warriors and shooters equipped with rapid weapons and pistols, and a healer
_41FF57345BA7524F	outpost_squad_light_mixed_fighter_e.outpost_squad	Squad of harriers	A squad of eight expert mercenaries, composed of warriors and shooters equipped with rapid weapons and pistols, and a healer
_430F573218985E38	outpost_squad_light_mixed_fighter_f.outpost_squad	Squad of harriers	A squad of eight master mercenaries, composed of warriors and shooters equipped with rapid weapons and pistols, and a healer
_5F89C5543EA54955	outpost_squad_medium_mixed_fighter_b.outpost_squad	Squad of fighters	A squad of eight apprentice mercenaries, composed of warriors and shooters equipped with light weapons and rifles, some carrying a shield, and a healer
_5CD1D9C771B7F828	outpost_squad_medium_mixed_fighter_c.outpost_squad	Squad of fighters	A squad of eight confirmed mercenaries, composed of warriors and shooters equipped with light weapons and rifles, some carrying a shield, and a healer
_50BE4B8DCDC79913	outpost_squad_medium_mixed_fighter_d.outpost_squad	Squad of fighters	A squad of eight advanced mercenaries, composed of warriors and shooters equipped with light weapons and rifles, some carrying a shield, and a healer
_E78BAAF4DA5C0763	outpost_squad_medium_mixed_fighter_e.outpost_squad	Squad of fighters	A squad of eight expert mercenaries, composed of warriors and shooters equipped with light weapons and rifles, some carrying a shield, and a healer
_278BA2E79E8CAB6B	outpost_squad_medium_mixed_fighter_f.outpost_squad	Squad of fighters	A squad of eight master mercenaries, composed of warriors and shooters equipped with light weapons and rifles, some carrying a shield, and a healer
_5C58BA5265E1368F	outpost_squad_nukers_b.outpost_squad	Squad of elementalists	A squad of eight apprentice mercenaries, composed of magicians skilled in destruction spells, and a healer
_F542B6ACE7A08614	outpost_squad_nukers_c.outpost_squad	Squad of elementalists	A squad of eight confirmed mercenaries, composed of magicians skilled in destruction spells, and a healer
_1626E063BEF34A1E	outpost_squad_nukers_d.outpost_squad	Squad of elementalists	A squad of eight advanced mercenaries, composed of magicians skilled in destruction spells, and a healer
_57E07466D6F2B724	outpost_squad_nukers_e.outpost_squad	Squad of elementalists	A squad of eight expert mercenaries, composed of magicians skilled in destruction spells, and a healer
_59E0746493E3C70D	outpost_squad_nukers_f.outpost_squad	Squad of elementalists	A squad of eight master mercenaries, composed of magicians skilled in destruction spells, and a healer
_20BF9A07073FAB16	outpost_squad_offensive_linkers_b.outpost_squad	Squad of disturbers	A squad of eight apprentice mercenaries, composed of magicians skilled in offensive link spells (debilitating and elementary), and a healer
_CA111D57F472AA54	outpost_squad_offensive_linkers_c.outpost_squad	Squad of disturbers	A squad of eight confirmed mercenaries, composed of magicians skilled in offensive link spells (debilitating and elementary), and a healer
_1B79E1F107A1070B	outpost_squad_offensive_linkers_d.outpost_squad	Squad of disturbers	A squad of eight advanced mercenaries, composed of magicians skilled in offensive link spells (debilitating and elementary), and a healer
_618979A3320EFB26	outpost_squad_offensive_linkers_e.outpost_squad	Squad of disturbers	A squad of eight expert mercenaries, composed of magicians skilled in offensive link spells (debilitating and elementary), and a healer
_638979A2EFFF070F	outpost_squad_offensive_linkers_f.outpost_squad	Squad of disturbers	A squad of eight master mercenaries, composed of magicians skilled in offensive link spells (debilitating and elementary), and a healer
_75DD5A02FC0EF85D	outpost_squad_mixed_casters_b.outpost_squad	Squad of magicians	A squad of eight apprentice mercenaries, composed of magicians who follow different schools of magic (destructive and relieving)
_7CBF364A9978C209	outpost_squad_mixed_casters_c.outpost_squad	Squad of magicians	A squad of eight confirmed mercenaries, composed of magicians who follow different schools of magic (destructive and relieving)
_270E0A5569E00C79	outpost_squad_mixed_casters_d.outpost_squad	Squad of magicians	A squad of eight advanced mercenaries, composed of magicians who follow different schools of magic (destructive and relieving)
_EED36269AEF31785	outpost_squad_mixed_casters_e.outpost_squad	Squad of magicians	A squad of eight expert mercenaries, composed of magicians who follow different schools of magic (destructive and relieving)
_6D029E6CE8731786	outpost_squad_mixed_casters_f.outpost_squad	Squad of magicians	A squad of eight master mercenaries, composed of magicians who follow different schools of magic (destructive and relieving)
_9F938CB2069C3115	driller_bountybeaches_kami_u1_100a.outpost_building	Offering for Tree-Bore	RM for crafting + Consumables 
_9F938CB2479C3115	driller_bountybeaches_kami_u1_150a.outpost_building	Offering for Tree-Bore	RM for crafting + Consumables 
_9F938CB206AC3115	driller_bountybeaches_kami_u1_200a.outpost_building	Offering for Tree-Bore	RM for crafting + Consumables 
_AC29D4E54FE02072	driller_bountybeaches_kami_u2_100a.outpost_building	Offering for Crystal Tree-Bore	RM for crafting + Consumables + Elevation Crystals 
_D5FED94E68A6D206	driller_bountybeaches_kami_u2_150a.outpost_building	Offering for Crystal Tree-Bore	RM for crafting + Double Consumables
_AC29D4E54FF02072	driller_bountybeaches_kami_u2_200a.outpost_building	Offering for Crystal Tree-Bore	RM for crafting + Consumables + Elevation Crystals 
_176386748322DF0F	driller_bountybeaches_kami_u3_100a.outpost_building	Offering for Hardy Tree-Bore	RM for crafting + Consumables (speed x1.5) 
_17638674C422DF0F	driller_bountybeaches_kami_u3_150a.outpost_building	Offering for Hardy Tree-Bore	RM for crafting + Consumables (speed x1.5) 
_176386748332DF0F	driller_bountybeaches_kami_u3_200a.outpost_building	Offering for Hardy Tree-Bore	RM for crafting + Consumables (speed x1.5) 
_10766E44DC25E6AE	driller_bountybeaches_kami_u4_100a.outpost_building	Offering for Superior Tree-Bore	RM for crafting + Consumables (speed x2) 
_10766E441D25E6AE	driller_bountybeaches_kami_u4_150a.outpost_building	Offering for Superior Tree-Bore	RM for crafting + Consumables (speed x2) 
_10766E44DC35E6AE	driller_bountybeaches_kami_u4_200a.outpost_building	Offering for Superior Tree-Bore	RM for crafting + Consumables (speed x2) 
_A5C73FC698518FF4	placeholder_bountybeaches_a.outpost_building	Constructible space	Come back to an empty space
_AC47886E6FE813AA	placeholder_citiesofintuition_a.outpost_building	Constructible space	Come back to an empty space
_F789BFC60F334EA1	placeholder_couloirbrule_a.outpost_building	Constructible space	Come back to an empty space
_8585E7E396EB9475	town_hall.outpost_building	Outpost Hall	Main building of the outpost
