outpost ID	name	description
fyros_outpost_04.outpost	Malmont Farm	Outpost founded in 2489, abandoned in 2494\n Challenge for expert-rank guilds\n An outpost constructed to the south of the Malmount and the Dragon's Tail, its activity concentrated on mining resources in this hostile region. A portion of its resources were transported to the village of Dyron and the two workshops nearby. The remaining materials were brought along the road to Pyr under heavy escort.
marauder_light_melee_fighter_b.outpost_squad	Marauder Warriors Squad	
marauder_light_melee_fighter_c.outpost_squad	Marauder Warriors Squad	
marauder_light_melee_fighter_d.outpost_squad	Marauder Warriors Squad	
marauder_light_melee_fighter_e.outpost_squad	Marauder Warriors Squad	
marauder_light_melee_fighter_f.outpost_squad	Marauder Warriors Squad	
marauder_light_range_fighter_b.outpost_squad	Marauder Range Fighters Squad	
marauder_light_range_fighter_c.outpost_squad	Marauder Range Fighters Squad	
marauder_light_range_fighter_d.outpost_squad	Marauder Range Fighters Squad	
marauder_light_range_fighter_e.outpost_squad	Marauder Range Fighters Squad	
marauder_light_range_fighter_f.outpost_squad	Marauder Range Fighters Squad	
marauder_light_mixed_fighter_b.outpost_squad	Marauder Fighters Squad	
marauder_light_mixed_fighter_c.outpost_squad	Marauder Fighters Squad	
marauder_light_mixed_fighter_d.outpost_squad	Marauder Fighters Squad	
marauder_light_mixed_fighter_e.outpost_squad	Marauder Fighters Squad	
marauder_light_mixed_fighter_f.outpost_squad	Marauder Fighters Squad	
free_squad_light_melee_fighter_b.outpost_squad	Militiamen Squad	A squad of eight apprentice mercenaries, composed of warriors and two healers, equipped with rapid weapons and light armour.
free_squad_light_melee_fighter_c.outpost_squad	Militiamen Squad	A squad of eight confirmed mercenaries, composed of warriors and two healers, equipped with rapid weapons and light armour.
free_squad_light_melee_fighter_d.outpost_squad	Militiamen Squad	A squad of eight advanced mercenaries, composed of warriors and two healers, equipped with rapid weapons and light armour.
free_squad_light_melee_fighter_e.outpost_squad	Militiamen Squad	A squad of eight expert mercenaries, composed of warriors and two healers, equipped with rapid weapons and light armour.
free_squad_light_melee_fighter_f.outpost_squad	Militiamen Squad	A squad of eight master mercenaries, composed of warriors and two healers, equipped with rapid weapons and light armour.
outpost_squad_light_melee_fighter_b.outpost_squad	Squad of skirmishers	A squad of eight apprentice mercenaries, composed of warriors and two healers, equipped with rapid weapons and light armour
outpost_squad_light_melee_fighter_c.outpost_squad	Squad of skirmishers	A squad of eight confirmed mercenaries, composed of warriors and two healers, equipped with rapid weapons and light armour
outpost_squad_light_melee_fighter_d.outpost_squad	Squad of skirmishers	A squad of eight advanced mercenaries, composed of warriors and two healers, equipped with rapid weapons and light armour
outpost_squad_light_melee_fighter_e.outpost_squad	Squad of skirmishers	A squad of eight expert mercenaries, composed of warriors and two healers, equipped with rapid weapons and light armour
outpost_squad_light_melee_fighter_f.outpost_squad	Squad of skirmishers	A squad of eight master mercenaries, composed of warriors and two healers, equipped with rapid weapons and light armour
outpost_squad_medium_melee_fighter_b.outpost_squad	Squad of battlers	A squad of eight apprentice mercenaries, composed of warriors in medium armor equipped with light weapons, some carrying a shield, and a healer
outpost_squad_medium_melee_fighter_c.outpost_squad	Squad of battlers	A squad of eight confirmed mercenaries, composed of warriors in medium armor equipped with light weapons, some carrying a shield, and a healer
outpost_squad_medium_melee_fighter_d.outpost_squad	Squad of battlers	A squad of eight advanced mercenaries, composed of warriors in medium armor equipped with light weapons, some carrying a shield, and a healer
outpost_squad_medium_melee_fighter_e.outpost_squad	Squad of battlers	A squad of eight expert mercenaries, composed of warriors in medium armor equipped with light weapons, some carrying a shield, and a healer
outpost_squad_medium_melee_fighter_f.outpost_squad	Squad of battlers	A squad of eight master mercenaries, composed of warriors in medium armor equipped with light weapons, some carrying a shield, and a healer
outpost_squad_heavy_melee_fighter_b.outpost_squad	Squad of heavy warriors	A squad of eight apprentice mercenaries, composed of warriors in heavy armor equipped with two-handed weapons, and a healer
outpost_squad_heavy_melee_fighter_c.outpost_squad	Squad of heavy warriors	A squad of eight confirmed mercenaries, composed of warriors in heavy armor equipped with two-handed weapons, and a healer
outpost_squad_heavy_melee_fighter_d.outpost_squad	Squad of heavy warriors	A squad of eight advanced mercenaries, composed of warriors in heavy armor equipped with two-handed weapons, and a healer
outpost_squad_heavy_melee_fighter_e.outpost_squad	Squad of heavy warriors	A squad of eight expert mercenaries, composed of warriors in heavy armor equipped with two-handed weapons, and a healer
outpost_squad_heavy_melee_fighter_f.outpost_squad	Squad of heavy warriors	A squad of eight master mercenaries, composed of warriors in heavy armor equipped with two-handed weapons, and a healer
outpost_squad_tank_b.outpost_squad	Squad of protectors	A squad of eight apprentice mercenaries, composed of warriors in heavy armor equipped with light weapons and shields, and a healer
outpost_squad_tank_c.outpost_squad	Squad of protectors	A squad of eight confirmed mercenaries, composed of warriors in heavy armor equipped with light weapons and shields, and a healer
outpost_squad_tank_d.outpost_squad	Squad of protectors	A squad of eight advanced mercenaries, composed of warriors in heavy armor equipped with light weapons and shields, and a healer
outpost_squad_tank_e.outpost_squad	Squad of protectors	A squad of eight expert mercenaries, composed of warriors in heavy armor equipped with light weapons and shields, and a healer
outpost_squad_tank_f.outpost_squad	Squad of protectors	A squad of eight master mercenaries, composed of warriors in heavy armor equipped with light weapons and shields, and a healer
outpost_squad_light_range_fighter_b.outpost_squad	Squad of gunfighters	A squad of eight apprentice mercenaries, composed of shooters in medium armor equipped with pistols, and a healer
outpost_squad_light_range_fighter_c.outpost_squad	Squad of gunfighters	A squad of eight confirmed mercenaries, composed of shooters in medium armor equipped with pistols, and a healer
outpost_squad_light_range_fighter_d.outpost_squad	Squad of gunfighters	A squad of eight advanced mercenaries, composed of shooters in medium armor equipped with pistols, and a healer
outpost_squad_light_range_fighter_e.outpost_squad	Squad of gunfighters	A squad of eight expert mercenaries, composed of shooters in medium armor equipped with pistols, and a healer
outpost_squad_light_range_fighter_f.outpost_squad	Squad of gunfighters	A squad of eight master mercenaries, composed of shooters in medium armor equipped with pistols, and a healer
outpost_squad_medium_range_fighter_b.outpost_squad	Squad of gunners	A squad of eight apprentice mercenaries, composed of shooters in medium armor equipped with rifles, and a healer
outpost_squad_medium_range_fighter_c.outpost_squad	Squad of gunners	A squad of eight confirmed mercenaries, composed of shooters in medium armor equipped with rifles, and a healer
outpost_squad_medium_range_fighter_d.outpost_squad	Squad of gunners	A squad of eight advanced mercenaries, composed of shooters in medium armor equipped with rifles, and a healer
outpost_squad_medium_range_fighter_e.outpost_squad	Squad of gunners	A squad of eight expert mercenaries, composed of shooters in medium armor equipped with rifles, and a healer
outpost_squad_medium_range_fighter_f.outpost_squad	Squad of gunners	A squad of eight master mercenaries, composed of shooters in medium armor equipped with rifles, and a healer
outpost_squad_heavy_range_fighter_b.outpost_squad	Squad of artillery shooters	A squad of eight apprentice mercenaries, composed of shooters equipped with machine guns and grenade launchers, and a healer
outpost_squad_heavy_range_fighter_c.outpost_squad	Squad of artillery shooters	A squad of eight confirmed mercenaries, composed of shooters equipped with machine guns and grenade launchers, and a healer
outpost_squad_heavy_range_fighter_d.outpost_squad	Squad of artillery shooters	A squad of eight advanced mercenaries, composed of shooters equipped with machine guns and grenade launchers, and a healer
outpost_squad_heavy_range_fighter_e.outpost_squad	Squad of artillery shooters	A squad of eight expert mercenaries, composed of shooters equipped with machine guns and grenade launchers, and a healer
outpost_squad_heavy_range_fighter_f.outpost_squad	Squad of artillery shooters	A squad of eight master mercenaries, composed of shooters equipped with machine guns and grenade launchers, and a healer
outpost_squad_light_mixed_fighter_b.outpost_squad	Squad of harriers	A squad of eight apprentice mercenaries, composed of warriors and shooters equipped with rapid weapons and pistols, and a healer
outpost_squad_light_mixed_fighter_c.outpost_squad	Squad of harriers	A squad of eight confirmed mercenaries, composed of warriors and shooters equipped with rapid weapons and pistols, and a healer
outpost_squad_light_mixed_fighter_d.outpost_squad	Squad of harriers	A squad of eight advanced mercenaries, composed of warriors and shooters equipped with rapid weapons and pistols, and a healer
outpost_squad_light_mixed_fighter_e.outpost_squad	Squad of harriers	A squad of eight expert mercenaries, composed of warriors and shooters equipped with rapid weapons and pistols, and a healer
outpost_squad_light_mixed_fighter_f.outpost_squad	Squad of harriers	A squad of eight master mercenaries, composed of warriors and shooters equipped with rapid weapons and pistols, and a healer
outpost_squad_medium_mixed_fighter_b.outpost_squad	Squad of fighters	A squad of eight apprentice mercenaries, composed of warriors and shooters equipped with light weapons and rifles, some carrying a shield, and a healer
outpost_squad_medium_mixed_fighter_c.outpost_squad	Squad of fighters	A squad of eight confirmed mercenaries, composed of warriors and shooters equipped with light weapons and rifles, some carrying a shield, and a healer
outpost_squad_medium_mixed_fighter_d.outpost_squad	Squad of fighters	A squad of eight advanced mercenaries, composed of warriors and shooters equipped with light weapons and rifles, some carrying a shield, and a healer
outpost_squad_medium_mixed_fighter_e.outpost_squad	Squad of fighters	A squad of eight expert mercenaries, composed of warriors and shooters equipped with light weapons and rifles, some carrying a shield, and a healer
outpost_squad_medium_mixed_fighter_f.outpost_squad	Squad of fighters	A squad of eight master mercenaries, composed of warriors and shooters equipped with light weapons and rifles, some carrying a shield, and a healer
outpost_squad_nukers_b.outpost_squad	Squad of elementalists	A squad of eight apprentice mercenaries, composed of magicians skilled in destruction spells, and a healer
outpost_squad_nukers_c.outpost_squad	Squad of elementalists	A squad of eight confirmed mercenaries, composed of magicians skilled in destruction spells, and a healer
outpost_squad_nukers_d.outpost_squad	Squad of elementalists	A squad of eight advanced mercenaries, composed of magicians skilled in destruction spells, and a healer
outpost_squad_nukers_e.outpost_squad	Squad of elementalists	A squad of eight expert mercenaries, composed of magicians skilled in destruction spells, and a healer
outpost_squad_nukers_f.outpost_squad	Squad of elementalists	A squad of eight master mercenaries, composed of magicians skilled in destruction spells, and a healer
outpost_squad_offensive_linkers_b.outpost_squad	Squad of disturbers	A squad of eight apprentice mercenaries, composed of magicians skilled in offensive link spells (debilitating and elementary), and a healer
outpost_squad_offensive_linkers_c.outpost_squad	Squad of disturbers	A squad of eight confirmed mercenaries, composed of magicians skilled in offensive link spells (debilitating and elementary), and a healer
outpost_squad_offensive_linkers_d.outpost_squad	Squad of disturbers	A squad of eight advanced mercenaries, composed of magicians skilled in offensive link spells (debilitating and elementary), and a healer
outpost_squad_offensive_linkers_e.outpost_squad	Squad of disturbers	A squad of eight expert mercenaries, composed of magicians skilled in offensive link spells (debilitating and elementary), and a healer
outpost_squad_offensive_linkers_f.outpost_squad	Squad of disturbers	A squad of eight master mercenaries, composed of magicians skilled in offensive link spells (debilitating and elementary), and a healer
outpost_squad_mixed_casters_b.outpost_squad	Squad of magicians	A squad of eight apprentice mercenaries, composed of magicians who follow different schools of magic (destructive and relieving)
outpost_squad_mixed_casters_c.outpost_squad	Squad of magicians	A squad of eight confirmed mercenaries, composed of magicians who follow different schools of magic (destructive and relieving)
outpost_squad_mixed_casters_d.outpost_squad	Squad of magicians	A squad of eight advanced mercenaries, composed of magicians who follow different schools of magic (destructive and relieving)
outpost_squad_mixed_casters_e.outpost_squad	Squad of magicians	A squad of eight expert mercenaries, composed of magicians who follow different schools of magic (destructive and relieving)
outpost_squad_mixed_casters_f.outpost_squad	Squad of magicians	A squad of eight master mercenaries, composed of magicians who follow different schools of magic (destructive and relieving)
driller_bountybeaches_kami_u1_100a.outpost_building	Offering for Tree-Bore	RM for crafting + Consumables 
driller_bountybeaches_kami_u1_150a.outpost_building	Offering for Tree-Bore	RM for crafting + Consumables 
driller_bountybeaches_kami_u1_200a.outpost_building	Offering for Tree-Bore	RM for crafting + Consumables 
driller_bountybeaches_kami_u2_100a.outpost_building	Offering for Crystal Tree-Bore	RM for crafting + Consumables + Elevation Crystals 
driller_bountybeaches_kami_u2_150a.outpost_building	Offering for Crystal Tree-Bore	RM for crafting + Double Consumables
driller_bountybeaches_kami_u2_200a.outpost_building	Offering for Crystal Tree-Bore	RM for crafting + Consumables + Elevation Crystals 
driller_bountybeaches_kami_u3_100a.outpost_building	Offering for Hardy Tree-Bore	RM for crafting + Consumables (speed x1.5) 
driller_bountybeaches_kami_u3_150a.outpost_building	Offering for Hardy Tree-Bore	RM for crafting + Consumables (speed x1.5) 
driller_bountybeaches_kami_u3_200a.outpost_building	Offering for Hardy Tree-Bore	RM for crafting + Consumables (speed x1.5) 
driller_bountybeaches_kami_u4_100a.outpost_building	Offering for Superior Tree-Bore	RM for crafting + Consumables (speed x2) 
driller_bountybeaches_kami_u4_150a.outpost_building	Offering for Superior Tree-Bore	RM for crafting + Consumables (speed x2) 
driller_bountybeaches_kami_u4_200a.outpost_building	Offering for Superior Tree-Bore	RM for crafting + Consumables (speed x2) 
placeholder_bountybeaches_a.outpost_building	Constructible space	Come back to an empty space
placeholder_citiesofintuition_a.outpost_building	Constructible space	Come back to an empty space
placeholder_couloirbrule_a.outpost_building	Constructible space	Come back to an empty space
town_hall.outpost_building	Outpost Hall	Main building of the outpost
